<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My City App</string>
    <string name="kavkaz_title">Hidden Garden</string>
    <string name="kavkaz_description">This restaurant is located in a beautiful garden setting and serves traditional Ilocano cuisine. It is a popular spot for tourists and locals alike.</string>
    <string name="kavkaz_address">008 Katipunan St</string>
    <string name="genacvale_title">Casa Jardin Empanada &amp; Okoy</string>
    <string name="genacvale_description">Craving authentic Ilocano snacks? This restaurant specializes in delicious empanadas and okoy, perfect for a quick bite or a leisurely meal.</string>
    <string name="genacvale_address">H9CQ+8JM, Mabini</string>
    <string name="black_angus_title">1995 Studio Cafe</string>
    <string name="black_angus_description">Enjoy a cozy atmosphere and a wide variety of food and drinks at 1995 Studio Cafe. From coffee and pastries to hearty meals, there\'s something for everyone.</string>
    <string name="black_angus_address">14 Crisologo</string>
    <string name="sakurada_title">Kusina Felicitas </string>
    <string name="sakurada_description">This restaurant is a great place to try authentic Ilocano cuisine. It is located in a historic building and has a beautiful view of the city. </string>
    <string name="sakurada_address">1 Bonifacio</string>
    <string name="beer_academy_title">Heritage Sky Bar</string>
    <string name="beer_academy_description">Heritage Sky Bar is a rooftop bar in Vigan City, Ilocos Sur, offering panoramic views of the historic district. Enjoy refreshing drinks and live music while taking in the stunning scenery.</string>
    <string name="beer_academy_address">H9CQ+6CX Calle, Crisologo</string>
    <string name="dargett_title">Lyric Bar</string>
    <string name="dargett_description">It is a classic bar known for its cozy ambiance and live music. Enjoy a cold beer or a glass of wine while listening to local bands or acoustic musicians. The bar\'s intimate setting and friendly atmosphere make it a popular spot for locals and tourists alike.</string>
    <string name="dargett_address">Lyric Cinema, Rizal Ave</string>
    <string name="lovers_park_title">Plaza Salcedo</string>
    <string name="lovers_park_description">This spacious park is a popular destination in Vigan City, known for its reflecting pool and nightly shows of synchronized music and colorful lights from the dancing fountain. It\'s a great place to relax, stroll, and enjoy the vibrant atmosphere of the city.</string>
    <string name="lovers_park_address">Burgos St. to the north and V. de los Reyes St.</string>
    <string name="victory_park_title">Vigan Fil-Hispanic Park</string>
    <string name="victory_park_description">This park commemorates the ties between Spain and the Philippines. It features a pool, picnic areas, and a playground. It\'s a great place to relax, enjoy the outdoors, and learn about the historical significance of Vigan City.</string>
    <string name="victory_park_address">H99J+RJF, Katipunan St</string>
    <string name="miniso_title">Calle Crisologo</string>
    <string name="miniso_description">Calle Crisologo is a charming pedestrian street in Vigan City, known for its well-preserved Spanish colonial architecture. As you stroll along the cobblestone streets, you\'ll be transported back in time to the city\'s vibrant past. The street is lined with colorful heritage houses, antique shops, and souvenir stalls, offering a unique shopping experience.</string>
    <string name="miniso_address">H9CQ+HF9, Crisologo</string>
    <string name="tsiran_title">Mart One Vigan</string>
    <string name="tsiran_description">It is a popular department store in Vigan City, offering a wide variety of products including clothing, electronics, household items, and groceries. It\'s a convenient one-stop shop with friendly staff and a prime location.</string>
    <string name="tsiran_address">1000 Rizal St.</string>
    <string name="rio_mall_title">Vigan City Public Market</string>
    <string name="rio_mall_description">It\'s a vibrant hub of activity where locals and tourists alike come to purchase fresh produce, meat, seafood, and other local products. The market is filled with colorful stalls and vendors selling a wide variety of goods, from traditional Filipino delicacies to imported items.</string>
    <string name="rio_mall_address">H99M+9WF, Alcantara St</string>
    <string name="vernissage_title">Syquia Mansion Museum</string>
    <string name="vernissage_description">Syquia Mansion is a historic house museum in Vigan City, showcasing Spanish colonial architecture and the lifestyle of the Syquia family. Visitors can tour the mansion, learn about its history, and admire its collection of antiques and artifacts.</string>
    <string name="vernissage_address"> Quirino Boulevard</string>
    <string name="cascade_title">Metropolitan Cathedral and Parish of the Conversion of Saint Paul</string>
    <string name="cascade_description">It is a historic Roman Catholic cathedral in Vigan City, known for its Baroque architecture and historical significance. As the seat of the Archdiocese of Vigan, it plays a crucial role in the religious life of the region. The cathedral\'s interior features beautiful stained glass windows and ornate altars, making it a must-visit for those exploring Vigan City.</string>
    <string name="cascade_address">Burgos St</string>
    <string name="northern_avenue_title">Parish of Saint Augustine of Hippo</string>
    <string name="northern_avenue_description">Historic church located in Vigan City, Ilocos Sur, Philippines. It\'s famous for its Baroque architecture and its elevated position on a hill overlooking the city. The church is dedicated to Saint Augustine and is a popular tourist destination.</string>
    <string name="northern_avenue_address">H9JR+FH4, Bantay</string>
    <string name="metro_title">Baluarte Resort and Mini Zoo</string>
    <string name="metro_description">The Vigan Baluarte Zoo is a small zoo located in Vigan City, Ilocos Sur, Philippines. It is home to a variety of animals, including monkeys, deer, birds, and reptiles. The zoo is a popular destination for families and children.</string>
    <string name="metro_address">Quirino Boulevard, Tamag</string>
    <string name="restaurants_category">Food Hubs</string>
    <string name="bars_category">Pubs</string>
    <string name="parks_category">Scenic Spots</string>
    <string name="shops_category">Stores</string>
    <string name="attractions_category">Cultural Sites</string>
    <string name="back_button">Back</string>
    <string name="next_button">Next</string>
    <string name="previous_button">Previous</string>
    <string name="categories">Categories</string>
    <string name="yerevan_title">Vigan</string>
    <string name="yerevan_description">Vigan City, a UNESCO World Heritage Site, is a charming colonial town in the Philippines. Renowned for its well-preserved Spanish architecture, cobblestone streets, and rich cultural heritage, Vigan offers a glimpse into the country\'s past. Explore historic landmarks, savor delicious local cuisine, and immerse yourself in the town\'s vibrant atmosphere.</string>
    <string name="members">Members</string>
    <string name="memberslist">Members</string>
</resources>